We've started the Nighttime and Idol Conversation Series, this is Kurumi Mori, nice to meet you!
And, assumeseseses Negishi Karun. Pleased to meet you.
19 Molt
Just around the corner.
Passed through.
Yes, that's right.
There was a group called Takoyaki Federation, wasn't there?
That's right. In Osaka.
So it's been quite a while.
It's been quite a while.
And it's been a long time since we've been out like this.
It's been a long time. It's been a long time since we've been together.
It's been about the same time since the last event.
It's been a long time since we had an event.
Minami Takaya. It's been a long time since our last event at ATC in Osaka.
I'm going to be in front of you all for the first time in a long time.
Yeah, it's great.
It's amazing. I've come this far with just "Un".
Aizuchi.
Stop it. Speak.
Speak.
Talk, talk, talk.
It's been a long time.
It's been a little while since I've been in private.
I've been seeing him. We've been seeing each other.
It's the end of the year, right?
At the end of the year, yes.
Second time at the end of the year.
First time this year.This is the first time this year.
Second time if I count after the event?
Second time.
I haven't said anything at all.
I'm scared. I'm scared now, too.
I'm scared.
Maybe it's because we lived together.
That's right.
We lived together and saw each other every day.
Your Kansai accent is gone.
What? You're kidding, right?
Yeah, it's gone.
I can't take it anymore.
It's really gone.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
I can't take it anymore.
If it were me like that, I'd forgive you.
Can you forgive me?
Mai would be so mad if she heard.
It happened the other day.
If I lost my Kansai dialect, she'd get really mad.
You got mad, didn't you?
I didn't get mad.
But you're speaking in Kansai dialect now.
Oh, really?
Yes, I do.
But Karen, you're in Osaka, right?
Yes, she is in Tokyo.
That's right.That's right.
But I used to check out Karen's work on social media and such.
Thank you very much. I have been checking it out as well.
I also saw her on stage.
Oh, yeah.
Kitsune?
Kitsune.
She played a fox.
They were all great.
That was, what, three years ago?
Really? Really?
That's the one with Mai and Sakira, right?
That's right.
Was it that long ago?
Not that long ago. Long time ago.
You came to see us.
I went to see it.
With Sakira.
Yes, the fox. Bakégitsune?
Bakegitsune.
I played a role, but Karen looked like a fox and she was so cute.
Because she was a fox.
It was amazing.
Thank you.
And I was telling her how amazing she was,
I told her that it was amazing, and she said that she had really been watching and studying footage of animal foxes.
That's right. He was watching.
A real fox, a real fox, even if it's a bunker fox.
Isn't that amazing?
Karen sounds like an idiot,Karen, you know, she sounds silly,
But she's serious.
Do you think we don't need an idiot?
I don't think so.
Oh no, I don't have the finished valve.
I don't like it.
You've already abandoned Osaka.
I don't mind if you do.
I really want to go home.
Really?
I tell my friends every day.
Come back anytime.
Send me home every day. I want to go back to Kansai.
I want to go back to Kansai.
Let's really go when you come back.
Yes, I want to go.
I really want to go.
But this is being distributed in September,
The month of the anniversary of the decision,
Isn't that great?
Yeah, that's great.
I miss it.
It's coming up.
September 17th.
That's fast.
I mean, you were in the seventh grade, right?
So?
I'm in the sixth grade.
Elementary school students are amazing, aren't they?
Even Sakira said she was in the 5th grade and 10 years old.Even Sakira said she was 10 years old, a fifth grader.
That's true.
There are a lot of girls now.
There are young girls, too.
When we said we were in the 5th grade, there was a lot of excitement in Cuse Mall,
Cuse Mall was buzzing with people.
It was like, "Why are you so nervous?
I couldn't figure out why I was so nervous,
But now I understand.
It's definitely unusual, isn't it?
She was an idol at the age of 10.
Isn't that amazing?
She worked hard.
She did her best. Really.
Because you and Karen have known each other since childhood.
That's right.
That's what I thought.
Karen was really,
When she was very tiny.
Around kindergarten.
You started, right?
She hasn't changed since then,
Fluffy.
Right?
It's like this.
It's not this way.It wasn't this way.
It's this way.
This is it.
It's fluffy. All the time.
But people from Wakayama..,
I think there are many people from Wakayama who are laid-back.
Oh, really?
Is that so?
I don't know.
There is only one wisdom in Wakayama, Karen.
That's right.
I heard there are many people like that in Wakayama.
Are there many of them?
Karen is a healer, isn't she?
Thank you very much.
She is a bit of a natural,
She is a bit natural, but sometimes she gives sharp comments,
It was like that.
That's how I felt.
I haven't been giving any comments lately.
I don't have anyone to talk to.
Karen, yes!
Karen, you've been playing games all the time, haven't you?
I've really become absorbed in it lately.
What?
She didn't come out last night.
You're day and night reversed, aren't you?
It's bad, isn't it?
I didn't sleep last night.
What?What?
That's why you're in such a makin' mood.
What's a makin' kin?
I'm tearing up.
I'm crying too much.
I'm crying.
I can't do it.
It's hard.
It's been a while.
I heard that while I was out of sight for a while.
I heard she's been shutting herself in day and night.
That's right.
Staff members in Tokyo
Please take Karen out.
I'm sorry.
But seriously, she can't talk.
I usually don't.
I don't talk.
I'm getting really bad at it.
You're kidding, right?
I'm stiff.
Don't talk with tears in your eyes.
I think it's September.
I have an event on the 20th of August.
I'm going to do a live performance.
I haven't been able to talk much.
I'm sorry, I touched the microphone.
It's been too long since I touched the microphone.
I'll be told I'm not allowed to touch it.
I've been told it's not okay.I've been told it's a bad idea.
I'm going to do it.
I'll do it.
That event is fine.
I'll do it. What's going on?
What's going on?
We'll play games.
We play with the guests.
And since it's probably over by now, I think it's totally safe to say...
It's a two-part event, with live music.
It's pretty grueling, isn't it?
Gutsy.
You can't do that.
I don't know.
Also, you know. Seriously.
I haven't been dancing at all lately.
It's so hard.
Do you practice dancing?
I do.
I didn't know that today.
I went again today.
Oh, yeah?
Go to sleep?
No.
You should sleep.
I've been asleep for 3 hours.
I'm not in bed. I'm not in bed.
I've been playing Pokemon Sleep for three hours.
Then I have to go to bed.Then I have to sleep, don't I?
I have to sleep to grow up.
I'm trying my best to sleep after eating Pokemon.
Even if I go to bed normally, it seems like I'm not really sleeping.
No, I'm not sleeping.
I'm just in a normal bed.
I can't sleep.
You're talking weird all the time.
When I'm asked to talk, that's all I can come up with.
You've become interesting while we haven't met.
You haven't met the members, have you?
I haven't met them.
I went to the collaboration cafe the other day.
You went there?
Yes, I did.
I like it.
I went.
Wasn't it the same before?
No, not at all.
Not at all. Before.
Isn't it bad?
How was it?
Normal. Before.
Isn't it bad?
Okay, so tomorrow we'll bring you the second part.
Please look forward to it.
So far, we've had the following partners
Holikurumi and
Nageshikane
See you tomorrow.See you tomorrow.
Bye-bye.